And that's why I will raise this in a way that makes us
So that I can go ahead and use her shop in being research methods
And
Then
So will i go into
The concepts of suspicion's hermeneutics and reconciliation and hermeneutics
And the concept of rationality or for something
As
A central component of hermeneutics to understand
In which way someone resonates
And that can be understood in different ways in the same way
The coffee break fulfills an important function
For students
Days
Geostorm space to talk small to know each other
And slowly with surely establish trust
And a friendly attitude to each other where one shares knowledge and cooperate or
What does the coffee have for function in the social system
Or
One
So to speak
Purpose statement
Christoffer
Drinking coffee
In order to
Show their affiliation to this to wash
Culture
Within the academy too common to stand and lecture with a cup of coffee in hand it is something that makes
One expresses
A way of being scientific academy, etc.
Okay three examples
So in some sense the modern home store is a
Modern
Invention
The modern her nail
Also have over the centuries
Been in a kind of low -intensity warfare or in what we then call for critical debate
With
Positivism
And on several occasions pointed out that things especially when it comes to it
Social or mental life and expressed soulful journey 70's words for
Social Darwinism
Change a little
To understand people and what they think and think and what they write and what they talk about and so on
Unable to reduce simple facts such as positivism did
Without
Decree
Something completely different
And here also this demonstration happens in has between qualitative and quantitative method is lost
Hard sciences it is someone who eats and roads and looks at simple facts and set them up in table
Or also further the causal relationship finds one
While
Hermeneutics yet will represent more soft science
We look at things that not necessarily
At the place where the mechanical scales such as
Humans humans conceptions of freedom
Man's conceptions of the social contexts she is part of
Swedbank
Is important point of view not because it is important that we have to put the name Schleiermacher on
The memory to probably so did not ask about it on the exam but
Schleiermacher
Designed
Lonely first personally about hermeneutics
Where he then
First, thought that when interpretative errors the stomach we have when interpreting the material misinterprets
It is clear that we can encounter new situations go to new places on earth where one suddenly makes completely
Other things are running so just yes
In Tokyo and so I would pay with my card and so handed over different like this
The card
And
Got back the card with a built in with both hands and then I realized
That I had taken with me completely wrong I had been very unusual as well as slender just raised my card and so on
And
Really, I would be polite and hand over one and both hands and not be as you are
When you walk on Seven Eleven on Vasagatan but actually consider that this situation may be different
When I buy one
Snickers basement coca-cola at a kiosk
If I do in Tokyo or with Gothenburg
As one can burst in the center high but we have anyway
The ability to learn to understand the situation all the time
What the girls thought I was interested in
It is only to analyze texts
Above all
And
Have something that one constantly here interpreting to try to understand what how relate to baby
Live our lives today so on
And
Then in relation to the text
So Schleiermacher thought that the goal of
The hermeneutics reconstruct the creation of it
That is
As far as possible
Repeat and repeat them
Thoughts that were behind
To
Da vinci code
Was written what was the writer thought behind then Vinci Code
When he wrote this way what was it
So which tank operations figure in the head
I recognize partly from the scientific method is like this that we try to understand
Why do any coffee drink or why vote someone for an exit from the European Union
Etc that are going on in the heads of these people around Europe
That makes the Soviet
We try to reconstruct their
Thoughtful or how
Partly in any case
This can do this with scientific methods
And
To do it
Where
If we try to understand why the North English farmer wants to get out of the EU
Why
Swedish Democratic voters
Skeptical of the after all with his folk party voters are positively attuned to the
Then you can go from my prejudices about Sweden Democrats People's Parties Word English Farmers and
London -based is the financier or how
Not say that much money by myself
Amber says about their performance world
So
Schleiermacher
Busy with the problem
Black displays oneself
If I will understand
Goethe
Navigate to writes their novels
You have to penetrate myself
And get good or maybe but at least to be part of it
The world of performance
I have to be part of the world of performance
That makes the north English farmer we go out after all
To understand
The social reality
From
The Conditions of the North English Farmer
How does a word in the English farmer look
On
At Brussels and politicians and how do they see the north English farmer at
Free market and so on can ask different questions and
Slowly with surely we know if we train ourselves
Farmer's
By the way
And
Have some kind of empathy
As a method
Solar
In the same way as that
Schleiermacher
Chiquito Z Express itself
So
Workers Bill Time with the initial understanding
To get into someone else's situation Visättra We cannot become the individual
The farmer
John Smith
Participants and bread for a quote I don't know on German original
But a discussion here between science and social sciences or natural sciences and those who lived in German
So Geist Wissenschaft
Kjell's sciences
As
Decor sometimes translates to the humanities but also is
Includes
Parts of the social sciences
We explain nature
We remember
Cause explanations
As
Wikipedia method literature
The hermeneutic circle
What is
Will drive to you when I say that the hermeneutic circle is basically the relationship between part and wholeness through unit is something
Now is starting to get tired of
But that's it
But
What is meant by this really there is a component in
The hermeneutic circle as absolutely central
An Easter bunny
So
Occurs
Knowledge in a kind of gap between me and they examine
In the same way
As the North English Farmer's
Attitude toward the arises between the farmer and the farmer context
We have
Double part of the whole relationship here
And what to do
If we are to follow dill pie
Is to become part of the farmer's performance world I will live in it
And then I'll get back and have to account for it and then it becomes qualitative science
Odeta
Should I
Idiot do
A type of
Circular movement
What do you do at home circle a circle a good concepts i would be spiral that i will soon be made
It might be one
Spiral changed a circle
So
Let's say I travel to England
Trips to northern England and start interviewing farmers and with u
I'll come then
Understanding
Or prejudice
I come and have my showing world
If
What means to be a farmer in northern England
I come forward
And is not starting to bid to talk and maybe even live with the farmers here I spend
Months
In theirs
What
Where is working on
How to measure how to sleep how then
The light of something new
If you can come home with my prejudice new as well as teach me new things about what means to be an angel
Peasant
Interpreters
It changes it in hospital
It is found on menu knowledge
And some of my performances that I had
For example
All enough English farmers
Smelling strange because they are out and keep up with all day
Maybe it
Falls in the light of new knowledge
I see that the peasants in northern England they do
Very much with paperwork finances to make their companies go around
Nordic farmers who are very active in local politics north English farmers perhaps also
Do completely different things that don't even involve animals they may not deal with it
Just up breeding sheep and such things one can do with tourism and such things
I learn lots of new things about Nordic farmers
And my parts
And my prejudice
Can be crushed
Others can be strengthened
But no matter what so my understanding changes
And circle movement anyway
Makes us imagine
That we start she is the starting point
Here I have only my
Performances
About Swedish peasants English farmers French farmers French Babblarna's notion that they are going and demonstrating in Paris Hill
A few days now, only two of the French farmers do this but it is the only thing shown on TV about Swedish farmers
That and romantically fine vineyards and such things
Way I have updated resource price mode so I have it the knowledge that
Connects I have
I go to England not we have the farmers
30 back again and
Clothes and not to the same place
By far a new flat
Turn off new knowledge New understanding maybe new prejudice new knowledge of something
Since
Passed that they should return to the peasants
Continue
Based on a new understanding horizon
Are you in
Commute back and forth and this I don't matter how to do interviews when interviews and in the past
On reads about that
Think more about what why answer
Or if i text analysis you return to a text man interpret
Because you read policy decision -making is and will interpret them
Or
Or you read different report
Etc
You analyze these with something special that we focus on something that is already issues
Then you can interpret the text and interpret the text to interpret the text you can keep on this
The monks of medieval Europe
Keeps up with their entire life interpreting the Bible etc. Returned Return Returned
All the time then
So change
The understanding because we fill up a new meeting with the text with man with interviews
With the culture that becomes studying them in anthropologists
Or
I return return we return to be heard again and retrieve circular movement that may not be a circular movement
Ways we can never get back to the same point a circle walks around around or how
Rather be seen as a kind of spiral movement
Where we hopefully
Gain a better understanding of you north English farmer
Or the one
19th century benefit or a no policy document or yet
Investigation that was made up of a department or whatever it is we write an essay or research on or how
Spiral circle movement
Is that as before our knowledge and makes the more scientific literature Petter
To also include reflection on
How we as a researcher go about
In this
The hermeneutic circle or what we should now call that spiral
About mine
Research you are about Nordic farmers
So I have a number of method rules because I will do it may have set up interview questions I might have with
Tape recorder i may have different things i imagine this of this this i shall look at
Here my analysis schedule this is my method of accessing you
Is the attitude of the Nordic countries to the European cooperation
I have
This
With me when I sit on the airplane at Landvetter and go to Gatwick 11 Avenue ended up somewhere
And a few hundred
Kilos of carbon dioxide later find me England and I have so to speak too
Research methods
Are, after all, impregnated by an understanding
Hello
We create our questions and issues based on something that we
Have read or
Namely
When we
Meets what we study
If it is Nordängen's farmer or an investigation text or policy document
Which
So we must be prepared to revise our methods as well
While we are researching
It might very well be like that
That I think I should
Ask five questions to the Nordic farmers that this will give me the answer to why they don't like
But once I get there
The question is misbehaved
Is not about
Complicated biographical papers from Brussels one had to fill in
It is not at all about what this is about instead
The nation's self -determination and the right to have a
Not to influence so that the decisions are made far away something there
The question of wrong
And the way I analyze it on
Nor was it very well in line with the reality I met when I went to northern England
Saga number said
We
Särdal 5 things on the checklist that we thought we would
Do that
We must, so to speak, as her think interpretative and within the qualitative method Anna was soft in
For the fact of being
Research instruments may have to change during the course of work
And when you conduct interviews, for example, I use qualitative interview
Then you will
Hopefully discover this
Bread before we write an essay that we know how to deal with this problem but you return and so
Press Play on the tape recorder and then you get on
Wait now I would I have asked a completely different thing here really it now realizes 41 degrees
We humans and we come on afterwards were mistakes
Idiot way so we are in a circle
Movement and can return and ask new questions, etc.
Practical reasons so you are kind so they have booked an interview that does not want to disturb people anymore and so you just say
35 weeks to write c-thesis etc so that
This is something that rather must speak reflective before
One that one can necessarily
Do if things say
Pam
Another concept as new
Perhaps encounter in the literature
Whether they read
Method literature or you read as more overall texts
The concept of understanding
Horizon or
Horizon
Fusion
And
Without horizon meltdown is rather about
Atman
So to speak
Can take to stand on that horizon
As
The north English farmer
Or
The London -based financier
Understand the world from the outside
And
Understand the world in that way but then
Not entirely clear
But
The goal of the research
Is to stand
On the same
Horizon to look out over type
English Channel based on Northern England
To understand
Power in Brussels
EU
Eevee practice based on this farmer's
Sounds super abstract or
Should I take it once again now another work
Or units
Why Dennis okay
Okay like that
I have a prejudice
If
I have prejudices about Sweden Democratic voters that they are low -educated
This prejudice I have and
I
Do you have the task to
Is related to a higher level of education
Then
I think
All the time then I'm going to the crushed revised here are also highly educated Sweden Democratic voters
As
Working strong e-education
Aspect, etc.
And then I can say reflect on
But why did I have that prejudice about low -skilled Swedish Democratic voters what can they tell me
About this one
To
Prejudice that I have received to me by the fact that
So to speak
Is in my bubble as
Academics or something like this by spending time with people who often say that the Swedish Democrats in Sweden
Team pictures hillbillies etc
So you prejudice has an origin in a kind of contrast that this prejudice might explain
Why these Swedish Democrats voters in some sense are so much against
This
The context that I come from
Of course
People who have prejudice against each other are often in some sense in different worlds or in conflict with each other
Advanced all the time
So then I can say use reflections on why my prejudice so to say what it was before
Origin and how they can explain
Start it
The contrast that arises in against the Swedish Democratic voter
It is something that anthropologists 118 20th century colonial anthropologists constantly wrestled with
But they went out into the British Empire and the German Empire, etc. and would study what they call primitive
Tours
They got there then of course I had prejudice
How many Therese anthropologists
Just went there and confirmed the prejudice and said that yes but compared to
The British formed man
So these people are just
Cdon button civilized
Others tried so to speak
Wait for their prejudice and understand thought system from within and understand how society
Built
And then when they returned
So
Related to
Run prejudice and so will
But it is not so much civilized that he fulfills functions that we can also see in modern communities, etc.
We also behave we also rituals in our modern societies for example
It's not just them
So -called primitive cultures that have rituals straight and so I also we also dance around the midsummer bar and all
Strange pagan things that really look completely bizarre in
But we have a notion of what it means to be a modern man enlightened man, etc.
Contrast
I stand and try to describe the world
What is it that affects this
This leads to the grand finale
Butter
The
The concepts of the suspicion's hermeneutics
And parish hall music
And to some extent the concept
Relativism
Do you want six minutes on me to pull this which is just too short
But there are places that I talk fast that can be found to reverse the tape
The Hermeneutics of the suspicion
It has been terminated in the book here
Apelgatan 8
Build on
A thorough with simple ways to explain the suspicion of the suspicion of the suspicion
Is
To think that
Fool
A people party
Goes out and says
We will raise the gasoline tax because we think about the environment
Then
Is there anything else that lies behind that
Suspects that this is really about a settlement Environment Party
Hello
It is so that I suspicion hermeneutics
First movement
That you don't believe it
That is on what one sometimes calls
So he is really exhausted and capital
I also suspect exaggerate and live a little here now but you understand the point like this
What is said is interesting truth lies on another level
Manifest level
Is
Only a shine
Because under this on it
Vegetarian
Tell a common perspective even though I survive little about in different discourse analytical perspectives text interpretation
Active looking for underlying meaning
We can look for underlying racism in texts we can look for underlying sexism performances
A little female and so on
In a text
We can look for different types without biology thus almost all ideology critical
Perspective
Is
Based on
Mistake
The opposite of MR not like this with coffee Personal Hemnet you parish home Rättvik
Or
Is there a position
From
Which
An interpretation is
More Sun more right more valid than another day
That is the opposite of
Relativism
I have to stop here
And
I hope to wish you all the happiness and hope it is as I have said